[
  {
    "question": "What is 'Um homem' in english?",
    "choice1": "A Cat",
    "choice2": "A Dog",
    "choice3": "A Woman",
    "choice4": "A Man",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 'Uma mulher' in english?",
    "choice1": "A woman",
    "choice2": "A Man",
    "choice3": "A Dog",
    "choice4": "A Cat",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you say 'a'?",
    "choice1": "um",
    "choice2": "ele",
    "choice3": "sim",
    "choice4": "nao",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 'o menino' in english?",
    "choice1": "The man",
    "choice2": "The house",
    "choice3": "The woman",
    "choice4": "The boy",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Translate 'menino' to english.",
    "choice1": "Cat",
    "choice2": "Girl",
    "choice3": "Boy",
    "choice4": "Dad",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 'Um homem' in english?",
    "choice1": "A Cat",
    "choice2": "A Dog",
    "choice3": "A Woman",
    "choice4": "A Man",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 'Uma mulher' in english?",
    "choice1": "A woman",
    "choice2": "A Man",
    "choice3": "A Dog",
    "choice4": "A Cat",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you say 'a'?",
    "choice1": "um",
    "choice2": "ele",
    "choice3": "sim",
    "choice4": "nao",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 'o menino' in english?",
    "choice1": "The man",
    "choice2": "The house",
    "choice3": "The woman",
    "choice4": "The boy",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Translate 'menino' to english.",
    "choice1": "Cat",
    "choice2": "Girl",
    "choice3": "Boy",
    "choice4": "Dad",
    "answer": 3
  }
]
